nationalcreditreport.com 2009-07-29

# National Credit Report Privacy & Security Policy

## Nationalcreditreport.com™ Privacy Policy

### The opportunities you deserve, the privacy you expect™

Welcome to the website of National Credit Report.com™ LLC ("Nationalcreditreport.com™", "we" or "us"). We've designed this website to provide you with access to credit management services, credit monitoring services, identity theft protection services, and other financial services and information. This privacy policy and agreement (the "Privacy Policy" or "Policy") explains how, with your permission (as set out below) we collect, use, and treat personal information that you may provide through our website (the "Website" or the "Site").

The terms "you" and "your" refer to any visitor to the Website, including (i) casual visitors to our Site, who do not participate in the products or services we offer through the Site ("Site Visitors"), and (ii) individuals who wish to participate, and register at our Site to subscribe to these products and services ("Subscribers"). For your convenience, Section 16 provides a full set of definitions used in this Privacy Policy. 

#### Your Consent 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully; when you consent to this Policy's terms, it creates legal obligations on you and on us. We ask you to show your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy in different ways, depending on your relationship to the Site. The procedures for consenting to this Policy are (a) less formal if you are Site Visitor, and (b) more formal if you are becoming a Subscriber. 

1.1.Consent by Site Visitors. By accessing and using our Website as a Site Visitor, you are acknowledging that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and agree to be legally bound by it. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please refrain from using our Site. 

1.2.Consent by Subscribers. If you register as a Subscriber, you will be prompted to click an "I Accept" button linked to this Policy during the registration process. Clicking "I accept" confirms your agreement to be bound by this Privacy Policy. 

1.3.Connection to Terms of Use. Clicking the "I accept" button will also further confirm your agreement to comply with the "Code of Conduct" and other terms contained in our Terms of Use. 

#### The Types of Information You May Provide 

Information you may provide while visiting our Site, or subscribing to our Site's products and services, or that we may provide to you on your request, falls into five categories: (i) Credit Report Information; (ii) Personal Information; (iii) Contact Information; (iv) Comments, and other feedback you give us concerning the Site's products and services; and (v) aggregate, anonymous information.

These categories are defined further, below: 

2.1.Credit Report Information. The term "Credit Report Information" means the information appearing on your credit report that bears on your creditworthiness, credit standing, credit capacity, personal characteristics, or mode of living and that is expected to be used as a factor in establishing your eligibility for credit or insurance (such as your credit score or information about your outstanding debts and payment history). The term "Credit Report Information" does not include information that constitutes Personal Information or Contact Information. 

2.2.Personal Information. The term "Personal Information" means (a) a User's first name (or first initial) and last name, in combination with (b) any one or more of the following data elements: (i) the User's social security number; (ii) the number on the User's driver's license (or non-operating identification license); or (iii) the User's financial account number or credit or debit card number in combination with any required security code, access code or password that would permit access to the User's financial account. The term "Personal Information" does not information that constitutes Contact Information. 

2.3.Contact Information. The term "Contact Information" means information you provide to us over the Site that would allow us (or others) to identify and contact you, consisting of your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number, and other contact information. The term "Contact Information" also includes information concerning transactions you engage in with us, or with our affiliates and business partners (such as your loan balance, payment history and other account information). 

2.4.Comments. The term "Comments" refers to feedback, suggestions, complaints, input, and other information you provide to us concerning the products and services available online through out Site, or that might in the future be offered online. The term "Comments" refers to that portion of your communication that does not consist of Contact Information, or other Protected Information 

2.5.Anonymous Information. The term "Anonymous Information" means information that does not identify a User, and may include statistical information concerning, for example, Users' participation in Site activities, or the pages on our Site that Users visit most frequently. 

#### Our Uses of the Information You Provide 

We share Protected Information you provide to us via the Website only as provided in this Policy. We collect information from Site Visitors and Subscribers at different points on our Website and through our Services, and use this information as follows: 

3.1.Registration Information; User Names. In order to participate as a Subscriber in our services, we require that you complete a registration form. This form asks for Contact Information, which includes such items as (i) name; (ii) mailing address; and (iii) email address. The registration process for certain services - for example services relying on credit reports - require a Subscriber to provide Personal Information, including his or her social security number. We use the information a Subscriber provides during the registration process (i) to provide a Subscriber with a user name and a password, to allow the Subscriber to gain access to Password Protected Areas of the Site; and (ii) to provide the goods and services the Subscriber has requested. We use Contact Information the Subscriber provides during the registration process, as further detailed below. 

3.2.Verifying Identity. When you order a product or service from Nationalcreditreport.com™, we may collect additional Personal Information online to verify your identity and process your request, beyond the data you provided during registration. This is designed to further protect you and to reduce the threat of identity theft and fraudulent orders of credit information.

3.3.Email Addresses. We use your e-mail address to send notifications relating to our Site, and the goods and services you have requested. In addition, we may use your email address, and other Contact Information, for the uses detailed below. 

3.4.Contact Information. To offer you all the greatest advantages as a Nationalcreditreport.com™ Subscriber, we find that sharing your Contact Information (expressly excluding your Personal Information), within our Nationalcreditreport.com™ family of companies and with business partners enables us to offer you personalized products and services at lower costs and/or much greater convenience than otherwise would be possible. Accordingly, we will provide your Contact Information to our Nationalcreditreport.com™ family of companies, and to our business partners. If you would prefer that we not share your Contact Information in this manner, please notify us via our "opt-out" mechanism, described in Section 9 (Your Choices; Opting Out), and we will remove you from this service. 

3.5.Account Transactions. We collect information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, and our business partners (such as your loan balance, payment history and other account information). We use this information in evaluating the types of goods and services you may find useful, in making business judgments concerning continuing a relationship with you, and for other business purposes. We may share this Contact Information with our affiliates and business partners, as provided in Section 3.4 (Contact Information). 

3.6.Promotions. We believe that our Subscribers' own experiences on the Site can often act as the strongest promotion for our products and services. To promote and illustrate our products and services, we may wish to post on our home page, on other areas of a website, or elsewhere, endorsements from, or other descriptions of experiences by, our Subscribers. You agree that your Contact Information and site-related experiences may be used and adapted for these purposes (without the need for compensation). 

3.7.Informational Notices and Bulletins. Periodically, we may choose to send news, bulletins, or other information to Users, and will use Contact Information to send such communications. If we choose to undertake such communications, you will have the ability to opt out of receiving these communications as provided in Section 9 (Your Choices; Opting Out). 

3.8.Surveys. Periodically, we may initiate surveys on our Site, and we may request Contact Information or other Protected Information from you in connection with such surveys. You are free to choose whether you participate in this type of survey. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and appeal of this Site, and for other business purposes. We will notify you of relevant details in connection with asking for you participation in such surveys. 

#### Credit Report Information Received From Others 

The information you provide will enable us to obtain Credit Report Information (including a credit report) on your behalf from the national credit reporting agencies. Nationalcreditreport.com™ does not share Credit Report Information except as permitted by law. As stated elsewhere on our Site, you have the right to obtain free credit report annually. Please follow the associated directions, if you wish to obtain free reports directly from the credit reporting agencies. 

#### Anonymous, Aggregate Information

We use Anonymous Information to analyze the effectiveness of our Site, to improve our services, and for other similar purposes. In addition, from time to time, we may undertake or commission statistical and other summary analyses of the general behavior and characteristics of Users participating in our services and the characteristics of visitors at our Site, and may share Anonymous Information with third parties, including advertisers (if any). Rest assured, though, that Anonymous Information provided to third parties will not allow anyone to identify you, or determine anything personal about you. We may collect Anonymous Information through features of the software that supports our services, through cookies, and through other means described below. 

5.1.IP Addresses; Logs. Either directly, or through our hosting service provider, we may automatically receive and record information in our server logs from your browser, including your IP address (the Internet address of your PC), your computer's name, the type and version of your web browser, referrer addresses, where the computer is routing from, and other generally-accepted log information. We may also record page views (hit counts) and other general statistical and tracking information, which will be aggregated with that of other users in order to understand how our Website is being used, and for security and monitoring purposes. 

5.2.Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to provide you with a tailored user experience and to make it easier for you to use a website upon a future visit. We may include cookies on our Website and use them to recognize you when you return to our Website. You may set your browser so that it does not accept cookies. Cookies must be enabled on your web browser, however, if you wish to access certain personalized features of our Services. 

5.3.Tags. We may use so-called "pixel tags" -- small graphic images (also know as "web beacons", "single-pixel GIFS", or "Web bugs") -- for purposes such as (i) to tell us what parts of our website have been visited, (ii) in connection with advertisements we may include on the Site, (iii) to measure the effectiveness of searches you perform on our Site, and (iv) for other purposes. Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format you can read, and they inform us whether emails have been opened, to help ensure that our messages are of interest to our Subscribers and other. None of this data includes Protected Information, and you can "opt-out" of receiving these types of emails from us by following the directions provided in Section 9 (Your Choices; Opting Out). If any Protected Information is collected using such tools, it will be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

5.4.Click-Throughs. We may send email messages which use a "click-through URL" linked to content on our Website. When you click one of these URLs, you pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply do not click text or graphic links in the email, or notify us in accordance with Section 9 (Your Choices; Opting Out). 

5.5.Banner Ads; Advertising Profiles. Our Site may include the use of ad banner partners for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions, and other marketing messages. These ads may be provided, in some cases, by a third party ad service provider or advertiser ("Advertisers"). These Advertisers may use traditional banner ads, or other advertising methods, such as advertising using profiles and related content. An Advertiser may place or utilize its own cookie on your browser, and may use Anonymous Information about your visit to our Site, such as the number of times you have viewed the advertisement. If the Advertiser requests that you provide to it Protected Information, please be aware that this Advertiser's use and collection of this information will be governed by its own privacy policy, and not our Policy. We recommend that you review the Advertiser's privacy policy before providing Personal Information. 

#### Use of Comments 

Comments you provide to us, to the extent they contain Protected Information, are covered by this Privacy Policy. Those portions of your Comments that do not contain Protected Information do not fall under this Policy, and instead are subject to the Code of Conduct and other provisions of our Terms of Use.

#### Any Information Linked With Your Personal Information Is Protected As "Personal Information"

To enable us to better understand your characteristics and/or to provide services tailored to your needs, we may link (a) the Protected Information you have provided; with (b) Anonymous Information. If we combine or link any Anonymous Information or other information with your Protected Information, the resulting combination will be treated and protected as Protected Information under this Privacy Policy. 

#### Disclosures to Third Parties 

At our option, we will disclose your Protected Information to unaffiliated third parties without your express consent in the circumstances specified below. We will not otherwise disclose your Protected Information to third parties. 

8.1.Site Vendors. We employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf, such as maintaining the Website, providing services related to the Site, collecting information, responding to and sending electronic mail, or other functions necessary to our business. We may need to share your Protected Information with companies that assist in the running of our Site (collectively, "Site Vendors"). We will provide Site Vendors with only that Protected Information necessary to perform their functions, and we will not allow them to use your Protected Information for any purpose inconsistent with this Policy. We require that our Site Vendors agree contractually to comply with privacy laws, and agree to maintain protections for your Protected Information that are consistent with this Policy. 

8.2.Government Regulators. We are periodically required to disclose certain Protected Information to third parties, such as credit reporting agencies, and federal and state regulators, in order to do business with you. 

8.3.Business Partners. In order to provide you with valuable product and service offerings, we share Contact Information (including lists of Users in a certain age range or geographic location) with our business partners. We require that our business partners agree contractually to comply with privacy laws, and agree to maintain protections for your Protected Information that are consistent with this Policy. You have the ability to "opt-out" of this information-sharing, by following the directions provided in Section 9 (Your Choices; Opting Out). 

8.4.Affiliates. Similar to the structure with out business partners, we share Contact Information with our Affiliates -- within the Nationalcreditreport.com™ family of companies -- in order to provide you with valuable product and service offerings. Our Affiliates have agreed contractually to comply with privacy laws, and have agreed to maintain protections for your Protected Information that are consistent with this Policy. You have the ability to "opt-out" of this information-sharing, by following the directions provided in Section 9 (Your Choices; Opting Out). 

8.5.Questions of Harm. We may reveal your Protected Information on a case-by-case basis to attorneys, private investigator organizations or law enforcement agencies if we believe (a) that you are in risk of harm from another, or (b) that you are harming or interfering (or will harm or interfere) with others, or are violating (either intentionally or unintentionally) our Terms of Use or are otherwise violating legal obligations.   
8.6.Legal. We will reveal your Protected Information, to the extent we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law. If we receive legal process calling for the disclosure of your Protected Information we will attempt to notify you via the email address you supplied during registration within a reasonable amount of time before we respond to the request, unless such notification is not permitted. 

8.7.Transfer of Site. We shall be entitled to transfer Protected Information to a third party in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of the business entity responsible for the information under this Policy, provided the acquiring third party has agreed to safeguard your Protected Information with protections that in all material respects are the same as or more protective than those set out in this Privacy Policy. 

#### Your Choices; Opting Out 

Because we respect your right to privacy, we give you the choice of how your Contact Information may be shared. Remember, we do not share Credit Report Information or Personal Information except as permitted by law. Moreover, you have the following choices with respect to use of your Contact Information: 

9.1.Opting-Out of Updates. If we choose to send to you bulletins, updates, product offerings, or other communications, we will provide you with the ability to decline -- or "opt-out of" - receiving such communications. Instructions for opting-out will be provided if and when we determine to send you such a communication. Please understand that you will not be allowed to "opt-out" of formal notices concerning operation of this Website, and legal and other related notices concerning your relationship to the Site. 

9.2.Opting-Out of Information-Sharing. You may choose to opt-out of our sharing information with business partners. Making this decision will prevent us from sharing your Contact Information with our business partners, and your choice may limit our ability to inform you of valuable and convenient products and services from these business partners. You may similarly choose to opt out of our information-sharing within the Nationalcreditreport.com™ family of companies. Making this decision will prevent us from sharing your Contact Information with our Affiliates, and this choice may limit our ability to offer conveniences such as a tailored savings quote on homeowners insurance, a custom financial investment plan, other financial service offers, and more. 

9.3.Opting-Out and Multiple Subscribers. For products and services that were ordered by a single Subscriber, but that apply to multiple Subscribers or other individuals, we will treat an opt out by any Subscriber as applying to all Subscribers (or others) covered by the products or service. 

9.4.Opt-Out Considerations. In today's ever-changing, competitive market, opting-out may mean missing timely information about money-saving products and services that help you accomplish your financial goals. It's something to think about carefully. We don't want you to miss any opportunities. No "opt-out" action is required if you want to enjoy the benefits of valuable product and service offers by allowing Nationalcreditreport.com™ to share Contact Information with affiliates and business partners. 

#### Access; Removing Information 

We provide you with reasonable access to information covered by this Policy, and provide you with the ability to remove and delete information from our Website databases, as follows: 

10.1.Subscriber Access to Information. If you are an ongoing Subscriber, you may have access to your registration information that is available online. If you have questions concerning access, or the extent (if any) of available access, please contact us as provided in Section 17 (Contact Us). 

10.2.Access to Credit Report Information. In accordance with applicable federal and state Fair Credit Reporting law, you as an individual have access (sometimes at no cost) to your individual credit file information either online, such as through [www.annualcreditreport.com](http://www.annualcreditreport.com/ "www.annualcreditreport.com"), or by requesting it by mail or telephone through the national credit reporting agencies. 

10.3.Deleting Information Provided Via This Website. If you have provided us with Protected Information in connection with your use of this Site, upon your request, we will remove this Protected Information from our Website databases. Please understand, however, that it may be impossible to remove this information completely, due to backups and records of deletions. In addition, please understand that, if you request deletion of your information, you will be unable to utilize associated features of the Website and any associated services. You may not remove de-identified, anonymous, or aggregate data from our databases. 

10.4.Limitations on Deleting Information; Public Databases and Non-Website Information. There are two general limitations on deletions, and opting-out. First, as provided in Section 4, please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy applies only to information provided through this Website, and does not apply to "Non-Website Information," which is information we obtain or is provided via other channels, such as public databases. Therefore, if we remove information from our Website databases in accordance with Section 8.5 (Deleting Information Provided via This Website), this will not remove Non-Website Information from our databases. We will retain this Non-Website Information in our databases, including Personal Information that may relate to our users, where applicable law permits us to retain the Information. Second, please be aware that even if you decide to opt out or delete information from our Site databases, Nationalcreditreport.com™ will continue (a) to share needed information with our Site Vendors; (b) to share information with third parties as otherwise required or permitted by law; and (c) to share transactions and account experience (such as the type of credit-related product you ordered or your payment history with us) within the Nationalcreditreport.com™ family of companies. 

#### Security 

We have put in place security systems, physical safeguards, technical safeguards, and quality controls designed to prevent unauthorized access to, or disclosure of our Subscriber's Protected Information. These safeguards include the following: 

  * Encrypting Protected Information with SSL technology while it is transmitted over the Web.
  * Enforcing physical access controls on facilities that store our Subscribers' Protected Information.
  * Employing firewalls and other technical protections, structured to prevent hackers and other unauthorized users from accessing Protected Information.
  * Providing clear policies and strong on-the-job training to our employees, to keeping Subscribers' Protected Information safe and secure.
  * Undertaking audits of our security practices.

Our security systems are structured to deter and prevent unauthorized users and others from accessing Information you provide to us. Please understand, though, that these safeguards are not fail-proof and, due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, we cannot provide, and disclaim (to the extent permitted by law), assurance that the information you provide us will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties who, despite our efforts, obtain unauthorized access. 

Moreover, please keep in mind that you also play a key role in protecting the security of information about you. For example, you should guard your password to our Site, and decline to allow others to use this password. In addition, you should close your browser when have finished viewing your information on our Website, to prevent others from viewing your Protected Information. 

#### Consent to Contact Under "Do Not Call" Registry

By clicking "I accept" to become a Subscriber on our Site, you hereby grant express written permission to Nationalcreditreport.com™, its Affiliates, and its business partners to contact you via telephone, mail, and/or e-mail for the purposes set out in this Policy, and you agree that these contacts will be permissible, even if you have placed your telephone number on the National Do Not Call Registry (or other such registry). BY CLICKING "I ACCEPT" AND BECOMING A SUBSCRIBER, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO RECEIVE CALLS PLACED BY - OR ON BEHALF OF - NATIONALCREDITREPORT.COM™, ITS AFFILIATES, AND ITS BUSINESS PARTNERS FOR THE PURPOSES SET OUT IN THIS POLICY. 

#### The Relationship Between Information You Provide At Our Site, And Information From Offline Sources

This Privacy Policy applies to information that you provide through our Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information you provide to us, or we obtain, through other means, such as publicly available sources, or mailing lists (collectively, "Non-Website Information"). This Privacy Policy does not govern our use or handling of Non-Website Information. If you, for example, remove your Personal Information from the files of this Website under Section 9 (Your Choices; Opting-Out), that does not mean your information will be removed from our files concerning Non-Website Information. 

#### Participation by Children and Teens; Advisory 

Due to federal law (as reflected in the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), WE DO NOT ALLOW INDIVIDUALS WHO WE KNOW ARE UNDER 13 TO PARTICIPATE IN OUR SITE OR SERVICES. YOU MUST BE AT LEAST 13 YEARS OLD TO USE OUR SITE AND SERVICES. IF YOU ARE BETWEEN 13 AND THE APPLICABLE AGE OF MAJORITY, PLEASE REVIEW THIS AGREEMENT WITH YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN. Please understand that we cannot necessarily tell if a user is providing us with his or her true age. 

#### Further Limitations on Scope of Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy applies (a) to an individual using our Website to request the Site's services and products for his or her personal, family or household purposes; and (b) to a business organization using our Website to obtain and analyze information concerning its own business. Certain practices described and rights provided herein may not apply to individuals or businesses that seek to use the our Site for other purposes. 

#### Notification of Changes 

From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. If we make any changes regarding disclosure of Contact Information (or other Protected Information) to third parties, upon your next login we will inform you of the modified policy. We will post notice of the new Policy from the privacy link on our Website. With respect to Site Visitors, your use of our Site following any such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Privacy Policy, as changed. With respect to Subscribers, no such changes will take effect unless and until you have provided us with your consent to such changes, in accordance with Section 1.2 (Consent by Subscribers). 

#### Definitions 

17.1.Affiliate. The term "Affiliate" or "affiliate" means an entity that controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with Nationalcreditreport.com™. 

17.2.Anonymous Information. The term "Anonymous Information," as defined in Section 2.5, means information that does not identify a User, and may include statistical information concerning, for example, Users' participation in Site activities, or the pages on our Site that Users visit most frequently. 

17.3.Business Partners. The term "Business Partners" or "business partners" means those entities with which we have entered into a business relationship, to develop, market, offer, or provide (a) the goods and services specified on our Website, and (b) other goods and services that we believe will be of interest to you. 

17.4.Comments. The term "Comments" refers to feedback, suggestions, complaints, input, and other information you provide to us concerning the products and services available online through out Site, or that might in the future be offered online. The term "Comments" refers to that portion of your communication that does not consist of Contact Information, or other Protected Information. 

17.5.Contact Information. The term "Contact Information," as defined in Section 2.3, means information you provide to us over the Site that would allow us (or others) to identify and contact you, consisting of your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number, and other contact information. The term "Contact Information" also includes information concerning transactions you engage in with us, or with our affiliates and business partners (such as your loan balance, payment history and other account information). 

17.6.Credit Report Information. The term "Credit Report Information," as defined in Section 2.1, means the information appearing on your credit report that bears on your creditworthiness, credit standing, credit capacity, personal characteristics, or mode of living and that is expected to be used as a factor in establishing your eligibility for credit or insurance (such as your credit score or information about your outstanding debts and payment history). The term "Credit Report Information" does not include the information that constitutes Personal Information or Contact Information. 

17.7.Nationalcreditreport.com™ family of companies. The term "Nationalcreditreport.com™ family of companies" means entities that are Nationalcreditreport.com™ Affiliates. 

17.8.Personal Information. The term "Personal Information," as defined in Section 2.2, means (a) a User's first name (or first initial) and last name, in combination with (b) any one or more of the following data elements: (i) the User's social security number; (ii) the number on the User's driver's license (or non-operating identification license); or (iii) the User's financial account number or credit or debit card number in combination with any required security code, access code or password that would permit access to the User's financial account. The term "Personal Information" does not information that constitutes Contact Information. 

17.9.Protected Information. The term "Protected Information" means the information protected under this Privacy Policy, consisting of (i) Credit Report Information; (ii) Personal Information; and (iii) Contact Information. 

17.10.User. The term "User" means both (i) Site Visitors and (ii) Subscribers.

#### Contact Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at: 

National Credit Report.com™ LLC  
The Preserve  
7700 N Congress Ave, Suite 3113  
Boca Raton, FL 33487  
[customerservice@nationalcreditreport.com](mailto:customerservice@nationalcreditreport.com)™ 

#### Effective Date 

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is December 1, 2008.

Copyright © NationalCreditReport.com™ 2009 .
